这是一个真实的故事
THIS IS A TRUE STORY
艺术家路易斯·韦恩
The artist Louis Wain
把这只猫变成了他自己的猫。
made the cat his own.
他发明了一种猫的风格，
He invented a cat style,
一个猫科动物协会，
a cat society,
整个猫咪世界。
a whole cat world.
长得和生活都不像路易斯·韦恩猫的猫
Cats that do not look and live like Louis Wain cats
为自己感到羞耻。
are ashamed of themselves.
但这不是最重要的。
But that is not what is important.
重要的是路易斯·韦恩把他的一生
What is important is that Louis Wain devoted his life
为了让我们的生活更幸福，
to making all our lives happier,
也更有猫腻。
and cattier.
通过这样做，他无疑在社会上掀起了轩然大波。
In doing so, he undoubtedly raised up the cat in society
他让我们的世界变得更美好。
and he changed our world for the better.
撇开它离奇的社会偏见不谈
Aside from its bizarre social prejudices
事实是所有的东西都是狗屎味，
and the fact that everything stank of shit,
维多利亚时代的英格兰也是一片创新之地。
Victorian England was also a land of innovation
和科学发现。
and scientific discovery.
世界上许多最优秀的人才
Many of the world’s finest minds